{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "6 + 53",
      "answer": 59
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 7",
      "answer": 64
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 36",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 67",
      "answer": 167
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 3",
      "answer": 21
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 99",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 4",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 23",
      "answer": 37
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 91",
      "answer": 174
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 76",
      "answer": 156
    },
    {
      "question": "53 + 76",
      "answer": 129
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 10",
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "question": "61 + 93",
      "answer": 154
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 41",
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 100",
      "answer": 130
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 42",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 96",
      "answer": 183
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 2",
      "answer": 8
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 76",
      "answer": 86
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 83",
      "answer": 160
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 72",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 66",
      "answer": 150
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 6",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 64",
      "answer": 110
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 82",
      "answer": 139
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 29",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 14",
      "answer": 73
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 82",
      "answer": 178
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 41",
      "answer": 64
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 75",
      "answer": 174
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 2",
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 51",
      "answer": 137
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 73",
      "answer": 79
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 3",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 14",
      "answer": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "60 + 35",
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 4",
      "answer": 54
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 21",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 84",
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 60",
      "answer": 129
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 8",
      "answer": 47
    },
    {
      "question": "73 + 11",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 4",
      "answer": 26
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 32",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 18",
      "answer": 43
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 12",
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 45",
      "answer": 62
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 61",
      "answer": 139
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 37",
      "answer": 52
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 31",
      "answer": 59
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 32",
      "answer": 42
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 26",
      "answer": 35
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 19",
      "answer": 33
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 75",
      "answer": 171
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 100",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 33",
      "answer": 53
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 52",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 11",
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 27",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 4",
      "answer": 36
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 45",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 77",
      "answer": 124
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 89",
      "answer": 173
    },
    {
      "question": "91 + 83",
      "answer": 174
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 87",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 33",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 36",
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 83",
      "answer": 163
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 90",
      "answer": 141
    },
    {
      "question": "36 + 28",
      "answer": 64
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 98",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "91 + 79",
      "answer": 170
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 53",
      "answer": 145
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 38",
      "answer": 65
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 4",
      "answer": 22
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 30",
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 7",
      "answer": 70
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 30",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 33",
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 95",
      "answer": 151
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 66",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "40 + 89",
      "answer": 129
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 93",
      "answer": 139
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 90",
      "answer": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "91 + 40",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 3",
      "answer": 62
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 60",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 27",
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 57",
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "79 + 24",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 92",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "question": "82 + 90",
      "answer": 172
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 92",
      "answer": 172
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 80",
      "answer": 163
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 24",
      "answer": 116
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 37",
      "answer": 43
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 20",
      "answer": 107
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 73",
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "question": "40 + 74",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 72",
      "answer": 94
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 4,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 300,
      "to": 400
    }
  }
}